好咧  各位都准备好干预一下玛蒂的行为了
Okay, so we are all here for Maddie's intervention.
我们一定要让她走进这间房间的时候
It is very important that we make her feel
感觉到这里是一个这是一个安全
like she's walking into a room that is safe,
充满着爱意和支持  小污点
and loving, and supportive and... Stains!
我真想把你手里的袋子拍掉
I am going to slap that bag out of your hands.
既然你不想任何人吃为啥还要把它们拿出来
Why did you put them out if you don't want anyone to eat them?
嘿
Hey...!
嘿啊
Hey.
嘿
你们在这干嘛
What are you guys doing here?
为什么都盯着我看
And why are you all staring at me?
为什么刚才维罗把前门锁了
And why did willow just lock the front door?
是啊  为什么呢
Yeah, why did she?
这让我有点儿紧张
It's making me nervous.
玛蒂  我们来这儿是为了谈谈你的问题的
Maddie, we are all here to talk to you about your problem.
什么问  我没有问题啊
What pro... I don't have a problem.
不  你有
Yeah, you do.
你对那些鞋子上瘾了
You're obsessed with those shoes.
我没有上瘾
I am not obsessed.
它们是我新的好朋友
They're just my new best friends
你的世界里唯一重要的东西
and the only things in the world that matter.
你以前告诉过我你多么讨厌高跟鞋
You used to tell me how you hated high heels.
我们周天的激励散步难道没有任何意义吗
Have our Sunday afternoon empowerment walk means nothing?!
呃
Okay.
我以前不喜欢高跟鞋  可是我现在喜欢了啊
So I used to not like them and now I do.
我说的是  一个女孩有权利改变主意
I mean, a girl has the right to change her mind
有权利改变主意了之后告诉她的朋友和家人
and also tell her friends and family
他们是多讨厌  别再烦一个可怜的女孩儿了
that they are annoying and should stop bothering her.
丽芙  是你告诉我去拥抱我的内在光芒的啊
I mean, Liv, you were the one who told me to embrace my inner sparkle.
是我说的没错  但是我发现我错了
I did, but I was wrong.
玛蒂  看看你  你现在的生活完全本末倒置了
I mean, Maddie, now your priorities are all out of whack.
你错过了一场比赛
You missed a game.
是啊  天  我都被逼上场了
Yeah, man. I had to play.
我进了个球  自摆乌龙
I made a basket... for the other team.
那我们说好去吃冰淇淋的事怎么办
And what about our fro-yo date?
玛蒂  那天冰淇淋还买一送一呢
Mads, it was two-for-one toppings night.
而且我讨厌你比我高
And I hate that you're taller than me.
这话真是出口为快
There. I said it.
我通过了往返跑哦
And I passed the shuttle run.
虽然和我们的对话并不相关  但我还是想说  我太自豪了
Not relevant to what we're talking about, but I'm just so proud of myself.
好了  伙计们  不过是一双  等等  你过了
Okay, guys, it's just a pair of... wait, hold on. You passed?
你知道吗  只要我想随时我都可以把它们脱下来
You know what? I can take these off whenever I want to.
哈
Ha!
好啊  那你脱啊
Okay, then do it.
恩  我说的是我想的时候
Well, I said that I can take them off whenever I want to,
但是我现在不想
and I just don't want to right now.
然后尼
So...
自己看着办吧
Deal with it.
噢  我们会的  大家动手啊
Oh, we will. Now!
迪吉  抓住她的腿
Diggie, grab her legs.
噢
Oh!
放我下来
Put me down!
这是怎  我的鞋子
Wha... my shoes!
丽芙  把我的鞋子还给我
Liv, give me back my shoes.
噢  松饼
Ooh! Muffins.
请别介意
Don't mind if I do.
丽芙  不要啊
Liv, no!
请别惩罚这双高跟鞋啊
Don't punish the pumps.
哦  相信我  玛蒂
Oh, believe me, Maddie.
这给我的伤害比给你的伤害多了去了
This is going to hurt me a lot more than it's going to hurt you.
哦  等等  我说啥来着
Oh... Wait, what am I saying?
难道丽芙·鲁尼能忍心
Like there's any way in the universe
可以毁掉一双超赞的……
that Liv Rooney would destroy the perfect pair of...
不
No!
这就结束了
It's over now.
一切都会好起来的
It's going to start to get better.
但是太难了
But this is so hard.
我的脚  要冻死了
And my feet are... So cold.
有些老朋友想打个招呼
I have a couple of old friends who want to say hi.
噢
Oh.
谢谢
Thank you.
哇
Wow.
我不知道我是怎么了
I don't know what came over me.
玛蒂  你找到了你的内在的光芒呀
Well, Maddie, you tapped into your inner sparkle.
是啊伙计  每个人都会这样
Yeah, man. It happens to all of us.
幸运的是  你有一个对这种闪闪发光的东西了如指掌的姐姐
Luckily, you have a sister to guide you through all things sparkly.
我们一步一步慢慢来
So we will start slow.
嗯  这是草莓味唇彩
Okay, this is strawberry lip gloss.
你可别把它吃了
Don't eat it.